<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
	
	
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">MBQs CPU Guide</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Options</string>
    <string name="version">Version</string>
	<string name="holo_theme">Holo</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_my_cpu_guide_">Welcome to my CPU Guide!</string>
    <string name="please_slide_right_to_open_the_menu_">Please slide right to access the menu.</string>
    <string name="cpu_governors">CPU Governors</string>
    <string name="i_o_schedulers">I/O Schedulers</string>
    <string name="tcp_algorithms">TCP Algorithms</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="general">General</string>
    <string name="governors">Governors</string>
    <string name="bfq_def">Gives each request a time budget. If the request is not met by the time it is given, the request is skipped. Smarter than the CFQ scheduler.</string>
    <string name="bfq">BFQ</string>
    <string name="android_tips_section">Android tips section.</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="autobrightness_info">Download an app called \'lux\'. It is an enhanced autobrightness app.</string>
    <string name="autobrightness_sucks">Auto-brightness</string>
    <string name="better_battery_life_content">TBD</string>
    <string name="better_battery_life_header">Get better battery life</string>
    <string name="block_ads_content">Download an app called \'adblock\' on the Play Store, run it normally, and accept the SU request, hit \'skip\' and run the program, exit out, and reboot!</string>
    <string name="block_ads">Block ads</string>
    <string name="brazilian_wax_definition">Similar to smartassV2, the only real difference is, it scales more aggressively than SAv2 does, which reduces battery life, while improving performance.</string>
    <string name="brazilianwax">BrazilianWax</string>
    <string name="cfq_definition">\'Completely Fair Queuing\' scheduler. Scales its requests in an effort to insure smooth task handling. Attempts to give each request equal I/O bandwidth. Typically, lag happens with this scheduler due to the effort of competing tasks on the disk because it tries to give equal bandwidth amongst all requests.</string>
    <string name="cfq">CFQ</string>
    <string name="change_boot_animation_content">Go to system/media, you\'ll see bootanimation.zip, replace it with your desired bootanimation, change permissions to r-w-rr (read-write-read-read), and reboot. (Assuming you\'re doing this on your phone)</string>
    <string name="change_your_bootanimation">Change your bootanimation</string>
    <string name="change_screen_density_content">In your build.prop, there is a line of code that looks like this: ro.sf.lcd_density=320, change it to 240 for a tablet feel. Don\'t go under 160 though, you\'ll get endless bootloops</string>
    <string name="change_dpi">Change DPI</string>
    <string name="conservative_definition">"Conservative means that it scales conservatively, not that it is conservative. It pretty much very similar to Interactive in that it scales up and down in frequency steps. It actually can be one of the most aggressive governors out there. "</string>
    <string name="conservative">Conservative</string>
    <string name="cpu_governors_content">Controls the CPU speeds and how processes are handled.</string>
    <string name="cubic_definition">One of the best, most recommended TCP options available. Less aggressive, Inflects the windows prior to the event. Used in Linux.</string>
    <string name="cubic">Cubic</string>
    <string name="deadline_definition">Set to minimize starving of requests. In other words, it is designed to handle system requests as quickly as possible.</string>
    <string name="deadline">Deadline</string>
    <string name="developer_options_content">Go to settings > build number... And tap \'build number\' 7 times. Go back, and you have now enabled developer options!</string>
    <string name="developer_options">Developer options</string>
    <string name="dyninteractive_definition">A dynamic-interactive Governor. This Governor dynamically adapts it\'s own CPU frequencies within your parameters based off the system(s) load.</string>
    <string name="dyninteractive">DynInteractive</string>
    <string name="fifo_definition">Takes each process in one by one, fair process queuing, balanced queue handling as well, processes go in and out in a numerical</string>
    <string name="fifo">FIFO</string>
    <string name="fiops_definition">Relatively new. No I/O seek time, ( potentially better for performance), balanced read/write times, one of the smarter I/O schedulers</string>
    <string name="fiops">FIOPS</string>
    <string name="force_gpu_rendering_content">What it does is, it force enabled 2D drawing (such as scrolling, and anything non-game/app related) to the Graphical Processing Unit, instead of the Central Processing unit. What does/can this do? It has the potential to save battery life, and takes some of the load off of your CPU, which increases overall smoothness and reduces lag.</string>
    <string name="force_gpu_rendering">Force GPU Rendering</string>
    <string name="help_section_content">TBD</string>
    <string name="help_header_in_layout">Coming soon.</string>
    <string name="hotplug_definition">Based off of Ondemand. It allows a CPU to go offline when under minimal usage. When you\'re sending messages, browsing Settings, or other simple tasks, most likely one of your CPUs will be offline.</string>
    <string name="hotplug">Hotplug</string>
    <string name="hotplug_x_definition">It\'s basically a smarter Hotplug. To my knowledge, it shuts off the second core much faster, and is a little bit smarter with CPU scaling and power efficiency.</string>
    <string name="hotplugx">HotplugX</string>
    <string name="hybla_definition">Penalizes connections that use satellite radio. Not usually used much.</string>
    <string name="hybla">Hybla</string>
    <string name="interactive_definition">Interactive scales by default in steps towards max frequency, Ondemand in its default implementation scales immediately to max frequency. (AndreiLux)</string>
    <string name="interactive">Interactive</string>
    <string name="interactive_x_definition">The same as Interactive, but when you turn your screen off it forces the second CPU core offline until the screen turns on again.</string>
    <string name="interactivex">InteractiveX</string>
    <string name="ioscheduler_definition">Control how incoming processes are determined.</string>
    <string name="i_o_schedulers_header_in_layout">I/O Schedulers</string>
    <string name="lagfree_definition">More aggressive kernel. It scales the CPU faster, reducing lag and performance, while maintaining decent battery life. Its main goal is to increase performance without reducing battery life.</string>
    <string name="lagfree">Lagfree</string>
    <string name="lazy_definition">This Governor doesn\'t scale as fast. It\'s really a lazy governor, it tends to stick in the same CPU frequency without changing as much. Which can be beneficial to your battery (if your CPU settings are conservative) or can reduce battery life (if your chosen frequencies are aggressive).</string>
    <string name="lazy">Lazy</string>
    <string name="lionheart_definition">Conservative-based governor off of Samsung update3 source (Line copied directly from a guide, thank you \'Amal Das\'), scales aggressively. This Governor is strictly for performance.</string>
    <string name="lionheart">Lionheart</string>
    <string name="lulzactive_definition">Based off of the Smartass and Interactive governor(s), the newer version of this Governor gives more control to the user, and he CPU frequency parameters (Ask for a description if you need one) are smarter. Smart at scaling both up and down.</string>
    <string name="lulzactive">Lulzactive</string>
    <string name="minmax_definition">Only uses your max screen on frequency, and your min screen on frequency.</string>
    <string name="min_max">Min Max</string>
    <string name="msaa_content">4 times MultiSample Anti-Aliasing. What this does is smooths out edges in apps that support AA. It makes your game look better, enhances graphics, but has the potential to degrade performance due to the screen enhancement. To enable this, go to settings>developer options>and check the box that says \'Force 4x MSAA\'</string>
    <string name="_4x_msaa">4x MSAA</string>
    <string name="nephilims_settings_content">Small Text</string>
    <string name="nephilims_settings_header">Medium Text</string>
    <string name="nightmare_definition">A modified PegasusQ, less aggressive (Which means not as good performance-wise), and doesn\'t usually hotplug. It is good for a balance between performance and battery life. May prevent the \'Screen of death\' as well, since it doesn\'t hotplug.</string>
    <string name="nightmare">Nightmare</string>
    <string name="noop_definition">It handles requests in a basic \'first in, first out\' order. So any requests that come in, will also be the first to be executed.</string>
    <string name="noop">Noop</string>
    <string name="ondemand_definition">Ondemand stands for that it scales up on load in frequency and then detects the load and scales back to a frequency which is fullfills the "demand" of the current load dynamically.</string>
    <string name="ondemand">OnDemand</string>
    <string name="ondemandplus_definition">A governor based off of OnDemand and Interactive. It provides a balance between performance, and saving battery.</string>
    <string name="ondemandplus">OndemandPlus</string>
    <string name="pegasusq_definition">Samsungs own Governor for multi-core phones. Based off of Ondemand. This kernel controls hotplugging as well.</string>
    <string name="pegasusq">PegasusQ</string>
    <string name="performance_definition">Will constantly run at the highest set CPU frequency.</string>
    <string name="performance">Performance</string>
    <string name="powersave_definition">Will constantly use your minimum set CPU frequency.</string>
    <string name="powersave">Powersave</string>
    <string name="reno_definition">Basically the same as Tahoe, but.. if 3 of the same packets are received, it will halve the window, instead of reducing it to one MS. It changes the slow start threshold equal to that of the congestion window.</string>
    <string name="reno">Reno</string>
    <string name="row_definition">Read-Over-Write. It will give better read times for pictures/media, but when transferring data/installing apps, significant reduction of performance will be present.</string>
    <string name="row">ROW</string>
    <string name="sakuractive_definition">A governor based off of hotplug and ondemand. The phone hotplugs (when it can) when the screen is on, and can be described as a \'hybrid\' of hotplug and ondemand</string>
    <string name="sakuractive">Sakuractive</string>
    <string name="savagedzen_definition">Based off of SmartassV2, similar to BrazilianWax, but this Governor tends to favor battery over performance. From personal experience, I can say it does a great job of doing so.</string>
    <string name="savagedzen">SavagedZen</string>
    <string name="scary_definition">Conservative-based Governor with some smartass features. Ramps speed up one at a time, and ramps speed down one at a time (ask for description if you don\'t understand). Caps your screen off speed at 245MHz. Scales just like conservative would. This Governor is more for battery life than performance.</string>
    <string name="scary">Scary</string>
    <string name="sio_definition">A mix between Noop and Deadline. Basic process/request merging. One of the most reliable schedulers out there.</string>
    <string name="sio">SIO</string>
    <string name="smartass_definition">Based off of the Interactive Governor, this is an older version, but this Governor is (or was) one of the smartest Governors, and is smart with performance and battery. More below.</string>
    <string name="smartass">Smartass</string>
    <string name="smartass_version_2_definition">A re-thought version of the original Governor. This one aims for ideal frequencies, meaning it makes up its own frequencies in order to meet the requests the CPU needs. Scales down the CPU extremely fast once the screen is turned off, meaning you will get amazing standby times. No upper limit for the CPU frequencies in both the screen on and screen off state(s). (If you want a better detailed explanation of that, please ask.)</string>
    <string name="smartassv2">SmartassV2</string>
    <string name="status_bar_tricks_content">If you want to access the tile settings quicker. Drag your status bar down with two fingers. If you want to bring down the status bar, touch the top of your screen and slide your finger down.</string>
    <string name="jb_statusbar_east_egg_">JB Statusbar \'east egg\'</string>
    <string name="tahoe_definition">Limits unknown packets being received. Limits the congestion window, and reset itself to a slow-start state.</string>
    <string name="tahoe">Tahoe</string>
    <string name="tcp_algorithms_information">Control incoming packets, and time-out connections are handled, as well as basically anything internet-related</string>
    <string name="tcp_algorithms_header">TCP Algorithms</string>
    <string name="userspace_definition">Rare in the world of kernels. Typically not used for mobile phones. But what it basically does is, it runs on whatever CPU speeds the user sets through an app.</string>
    <string name="userspace">Userspace</string>
    <string name="vegas_definition">One of the smoothest (next to cubic), it increases the time-out delay for packets, which allows more to be received, but at a higher rate. It also has set time-outs, which helps with speed because it\'s constantly being refreshed.</string>
    <string name="vegas">Vegas</string>
    <string name="vr_definition">Best for benchmarks due to performance of requests, but is considered unstable due to random drops in performance. Semi-based off of the CFQ scheduler.</string>
    <string name="v_r_">V(R)</string>
    <string name="westwood_definition">A newer version of Reno, and another commonly used one. It controls parameters better, helping out streaming and overall quality of browsing the internet. One of the most \'fair\' algorithms out there, and is one of the most efficient algorithms to date.</string>
    <string name="westwood">Westwood</string>
    <string name="wifi_scan_interval_content">Before you freak out, I will give you what it means. What it means is this: how often your phone scans for a WiFi signal. Typically, it is 15 seconds. The recommended number is 300. To change it, you can typically find it in the build.prop manually edit it on your computer, or use an app such as ES file explorer and run it as root. Go to build.prop and look for: wifi.supplicant_scan_interval=x. And change x (usually 15) to 300, save, exit, and reboot. Please note it is not available with some ROMs that are driven towards a stock-ish feeling. Such as CM ROMs, or any derivative of that ROM.</string>
    <string name="wifi_scan_interval">Wifi scan interval</string>
    <string name="wifi_sleep_policy_content">Kkeeps WiFi on while your phone is awake. To enable this, (and there are many ways.. I\'ll give you the way I\'d do it.) Go to settings>WiFi>WiFi settings (3 vertical dots)>Advanced settings > keep WiFi on during sleep.. And set it to \'always\' or, You can use TricksterMOD and enable that via the GUI (Graphic User Interface)</string>
    <string name="wifi_on_during_sleep">WiFi on during sleep</string>
    <string name="zram_information_content">Avoids disk paging, compresses your RAM. Disk paging means the way your phone saves temporary data. It helps with fragmentation of your disk and the physical space, which, over time, keeps speed stable and prevents any system slowdowns.</string>
    <string name="zram_information">zRAM Information</string>   
	
</resources>
